Guide to the Associates of the Stanford University Libraries Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Oversize Materials, Series 7
  - Keepsake: printed on the visit of The Friends of Stanford Library Assocation to The Whittington Press on 30 April, 1978 (Box 26)
  - Keepsake: When Grog May Be Taken Medicinally, for joint meeting of the Zamarano and Roxburghe clubs, Los Angeles, October, 1986 (Box 26)
- Memorabilia, Series 8
  - Vendor tag for Kathy Cusic (probably from a book fair) (Box 27)
  - Wooden gavel, "ASUL" carved on head (Box 27)
- Additional Records, Accession 2010-131
  - Correspondence (including Lawrence Clark Powell and Wallace Stegner) and other records, 1973-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (including David Perty and Frederick B. Adams) and other records, 1973-1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, administrative, 1995-96 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Furbush, Marnie, correspondence, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Wilson, Adrian, correspondence, keepsake, clipping, 1972-1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hanna, Paul R., "Remembering Our Roots,", 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Warren Howell Award, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Clippings and articles, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - ASUL Gifts to the Stanford University Libraries 1973-1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, agendas, correspondence, 1990-1999 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, agendas, memos, etc., 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Minutes, agendas, materials re proposed Michigan trip, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous records, 1981-1997 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Portugal trip, backgrond information and correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Study Tour to London and Oxford, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - South Florida trip, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Sonoma trip, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Dickens trip, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Dickens trip, travel booklets and brochures, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Book Fair, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Literary Journey to New England, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Literary Journey to New England, travel brochures, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - California Historical Society reception, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Humboldt County trip, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Southern California Bookland trip, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - San Francisco Book Fair, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Program planning and other records, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Texas trip, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Literary Pennsylvania reunion, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Photo album: Literary Journey to Virginia, 1988 April-May (Box 4)
  - Photo album: Journey to Ireland and Scotland, 1987 May (Box 4)
  - Photo Album: Southern California Bookland Tour, 1995 April (Box 4)
  - Photographs: party following talk by Carlos Baker, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Photographs: ASUL picnic3, 1985 and undated (Box 4)
  - Photographs: Monterey and vist to Steinbeck Library, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Photographs: ASUL events, assorted, 1991 and undated (Box 4)
  - Photographs: Literary Journey to New England, 1996 May (Box 4)
  - Oversize photograph: Hildegarde Teilet at her home with Byra Wreden and others, undated (Box 4)
  - Photo albums (2): Literary Journey to England and Charles Dickens, 1997 June (Box 5)
  - Photo album: Literary Journey to New England, 1996 May (Box 5)
  - Photographs: Literary Journey to England and Charles Dickens, 1997 June (Box 5)